Kotori Itsuka.
Um, is it too late to get off? I want off.
Oh, it's way too late.
More often than not, feelings have a way of complicating things.
The red flame has forgotten the truth, while the white flame has discovered it.
And when these two flames meet, everything will burn to ash.
All the air from the air from the cloudszurum.
The two winds have observed it perfectly.
Oh
These rides are so stupid
Yeah
I
Wonder if Shida will survive this she's mad
Actually
This might end up being exactly what Coterie needed
I
Think he just made the perfect call
We've blown this date out of proportion instead of letting it be
I hope you're right
Are you scared?
Give me your hand
What for? I'm not some frightened kid you know
Unless
You're the one who's actually freaking out
You scared?
Yes that's it
Please hold hands with me I'm so scared
Stop acting like a weirdo
Oh please Coterie hold my hand I'm so scared
Fine if you'll shut up
She don't know what a waste
If you hugged the commander
You could legitimately enjoy her soft supple body
You just lost the perfect opportunity to get a foot planted right into your face
Why? Why are you riding together?
You should let the commander drive the car by herself you idiot
That way you could be running in front of her as a personal target
Imagine the gradually shrinking distance as the commander smiles sadistically
Trying to run you down and crush your dreams
Oh
Mercy my sweet commander have mercy
Oh have mercy
Shida was right
Throwing out his headset was a good call
Wow this jungle cruise is everything Shida said it would be
Yes it is I'm having fun
Feels good to relax
Don't you think it would be even more fun if Shida and Coterie were with us though?
Why didn't they want to come too?
Wait, why don't we go get them?
You can't do that Choka
Why not? We should all be having a good time together
Yeah, but that's not it
We might have overheard something kind of major
Coterie's really a spirit?
Shida's trying to save her
He's going to seal her power away like he did with both of us
He needs this time
So we shouldn't interrupt him
We've gotta let him do what he needs to
We heard that if he fails they don't know what will happen to Coterie
Chances are it's not good
We need to stay away Toka
Yeah, okay, I guess you're right
But I do wish there was something we could do to help them
I owe Coterie so much for what she's given me
It's hard to just sit here
Besides, I like Coterie a lot
Don't you think she has the same kind of smell as Shida?
That's probably because they use the same shampoo!
We have to let Shida handle this
It's the best thing for Coterie
We've got an emergency here
DW-029 has disappeared
No evidence of a transport vehicle
The white licorice battle suit has been stolen
Whoever has it took all the ammunition as well
It isn't ready for field use yet
The deployment inspection made that very clear
Do you think it would be possible to even defeat Ifrit using this?
Origami
Man, I underestimated this theme park
Talk about a good time
You are so immature
Maybe try to get out of those diapers before you graduate
This from the girl who was freaking out about a water slide?
You mean death trap!
Well, whatever, I'm over it
And besides, at least it wasn't totally boring, you know?
Yep, that's true
It's been a long time, right?
Since we've been to a theme park like this
I can't remember though, do you know?
Yeah, five years
Really? That long?
Spirits killed my parents, they burned them
Five years ago, somehow I became a flame spirit
What is it?
Oh, is it happening now?
Kotari?
Yeah! What is it?
Uh, look Shido, I... I think...
Well, this is just as good of a time as any, but...
I just, um, I want to go somewhere with fewer people because I'm really embarrassed
Why?
Uh, it's not obvious
We'll be okay right here, I promise you
Now, listen, Kotari?
Yeah, what?
I have a question
You can't just ask me like that, it's super awkward
Uh, wait
No!
Never mind, ignore me
I'm alright, so please just hurry up and ask your question
Yeah, okay
So listen
About... five years
Kotari!
Shido! It's dangerous here!
You need to leave!
Horigami?
Horigami!
Why?
Do you have any idea what you just did?
Yes, Kotari is dead
I killed her
Heh! You killed me?
You don't make it sound like it was that big of a deal
I'm disappointed
I thought you were smarter than that, but apparently I was giving you far too much credit
Who knew you would get a hold of a missile?
And who knew you were crazy enough to use it?
Especially when you consider how many innocent people are around us
No!
Elohim Kibol
Come on!
I found you!
Finally!
Ah!
I found you
Finally!
Ah!
Kodari!
Aragami!
Stop!
Ah!
You have to stop this!
Please, stop!
It feels weird
I know!
Come on!
Let's go!
I know. Come on, let's go.
Hey, what are you doing, Yoshinan?
You can't go, Toga.
Remember, your powers are sealed inside Shido right now,
so you might not even be able to protect yourself.
Whoever that is has to be pretty strong to create such a big explosion.
If you go, there's no guarantee you'll come back alive.
I appreciate the warning, but I'm not making Shido face that alone.
But Toga...
Shido is trying to save my friend Kotori.
He won't give up on her.
Me neither. Let's go.
Hey, Yoshinan.
I am... well, can I go?
If you feel that strongly about it, I won't stop you.
Why on earth would you choose to use such an ill-behaving weapon?
Deploying territory. Locking coordinates.
Shockingly not too bad.
I haven't seen that suit before. It must be a new one.
No. I've used too much power.
Kotori!
Leave, leave, ready!
Fire!
Deploying territory.
Blast Ark ready!
Annihilate her!
Kokori!
Protect territory! Deploy!
Oh, no. Where did all your power go?
You're going to beat me, right?
You're going to shoot me, right?
You're going to kill me, right?
Then stop stalling.
Go on. Take aim before it's too late.
Otherwise...
You'll be dead before you know what hit you.
Kotori, stop it!
What? Finished already?
That's no fun at all.
Come on.
Make it open.
Do something.
Because if you don't,
I have absolutely no use for you.
I said knock it off!
Damn you, Efreet.
Sounds practically dreadful, don't you think?
Where did you hear about my little nickname?
This is how you did it, isn't it?
This is how you murdered my parents five years ago!
What do you mean?
Five years ago,
my parents were brutally killed by a flame spirit.
I watched as you murdered them.
I remember everything.
How could I forget that, though?
How could anyone?
Now you'll pay.
This is where you die!
And I'm the one who's going to kill you!
No, I don't...
You're lying.
This time I won't miss!
Kotori, no!
Territory condensed.
White licorice.
Critical driving force.
Origami, please stop!
You can't do this!
Shino, get out of my way!
Like hell I will!
I told you,
since they died,
my only purpose in life has been to avenge my parents.
Killing Efreet,
killing Kotori,
is the only reason I have for living!
You can't.
You can't kill my sister!
If you pull that trigger,
there's no going back.
I do this all the time.
I don't want to see you end up like Mana!
I don't care what you want.
My goal is to kill Efreet with my own hands!
Origami,
just answer one thing.
You're only after Efreet, right?
You want the flame spirit.
You're not after my little sister at all.
You don't want to kill Kotori Itsuka, do you?
What are you talking about?
Just answer me!
You're after the flame spirit,
and my little sister has nothing to do with it.
Isn't that right?
You're not making any sense, Shido.
Yes,
I am after Efreet,
the flame spirit.
But your little sister is a spirit.
No matter what you say,
that is a fact.
So please,
get out of my way!
Just wait!
Origami,
I need you to give me some time!
No!
This is my best chance to take her down,
and I'm not throwing that away!
Listen to me!
I know it sounds like an excuse,
but I'm not about to just sit here
while you murder my little sister!
And on top of that,
I can't do nothing
while my friend is in so much pain.
Yes,
even so.
Origami!
Toka?
Yoshido?
We're here.
Are you okay?
Wahoo!
Saved you!
Don't worry,
you can thank us later!
Yoshido,
not now.
Move!
Shido!
Take Kotori and get out of here!
We can take care of this!
Wait!
Are you sure?
Yes!
Now go!
Hurry!
I can't last much longer!
Thank you!
I don't have time
to screw around with you!
I can screw around with you, too!
Come on, Origami!
You have to stop this!
There's no point in killing Kotori!
You don't know what you're talking about!
Yes,
I do!
Don't you remember?
You shot Shido!
We both thought you had killed him!
It was so painful!
I'd never felt that sad before!
I felt broken,
and more alone than ever!
Isn't that how you felt
when you lost your parents?
Do you really want to put Shido
through that kind of pain?
Because that's not fair!
You're being selfish!
Why wouldn't you want to hurt
such wonderful people?
Promise me something.
Promise you'll stop hurting good people.
Shido, I'm so sorry about this.
Don't worry about it.
I'll figure something out.
Look, sis.
Yeah?
How am I supposed to confirm
Kotori's happiness meter
without getting in touch with Reina?
I have to seal her power,
and I have to do it now.
It breaks!
Focus on me!
Kotori,
the truth is,
well,
you'll always be
my favorite little sister.
I'm prouder of you
than you will ever understand.
I adore everything about you.
And I...
I love you.
Really?
What about you?
How do you feel about me?
Um,
is this kind of an awkward time to ask?
Kotori!
I feel the same way!
I love you, too!
I've always loved you!
I love you more than anything!
I love you!
Do you remember now?
Five years ago, I saw her.
There was someone else.
Shido!
What just happened?
Origami, you said it yourself.
You're after Ifrit.
The flame spirit is the one you want.
You don't want to hurt my sister.
She's not a spirit anymore.
She's human.
So come on, change your aim.
I'm Ifrit now, target me!
I don't understand.
What are you saying?
I remember.
I know what really happened five years ago.
I know what we did.
But Ifrit killed my parents!
You are right that Ifrit was the reason the fire started.
But understand, Kotari didn't kill anyone.
No, that can't be!
I know I saw a spirit that day!
Yes, there was one there.
It's the same spirit that made Kotari suffer through all of this.
Do you really expect me to believe you?
Yeah.
I want to.
But I...
I just can't!
If that's the case, then you don't have a choice.
Shoot me.
Kill Ifrit.
Come on.
You've said it before, right?
No one should ever have to feel the way I felt that day.
Activation limit!
No!
I won't be stopped now!
Put the gun down!
You can't take Kotari away from me!
She saved my life!
If it weren't for her, I wouldn't be here!
Believe me.
Please, you have to believe me.
No!
I can't let go!
Well, that's not going to be nearly enough.
Shin, I'm so sorry.
I'm entirely responsible for what happened today.
You mean because you had Toka and Yoshino go on the date?
That wasn't all that bad.
No.
I should never have sent you out on that date in the first place.
Instead, I should have had you seal her powers as soon as you woke up yesterday.
But Kotari was so excited about the date.
I don't know.
I just couldn't take that away from her.
Oh.
But even so, that was impossible, right?
Her happiness meter, it wasn't even full.
What is this?
These are all the changes we recorded in Kotari's feelings towards you since we measured her yesterday.
As you can see, they haven't changed in the least.
They've been maxed out the whole time.
She told you as much herself, didn't she?
Kotari loves her big brother more than anything.
Something must be broken!
There's no way those stupid measurements are right!
Not true.
There's nothing wrong with the measurements.
Say the numbers are off or buy me a dozen cream puffs!
My apologies, Shin.
The measurements are wrong.
Fine.
Whatever.
Anyway, you sure you're all right?
Shouldn't you be resting or not kicking me?
Don't have that kind of time.
I have a long report to write, you know.
We finally got our memories back.
But they could always be erased again.
If we want to make sure we can remember what really happened to us five years ago,
then it would probably be smart to record the truth somewhere other than either one of our two heads.
Understood.
Don't work too hard.
I won't.
Oh, Shido.
You know what you said before you sealed my spirit power?
Was that true?
Well, yeah, of course it was.
I do love you.
I always will.
Uh, I was wondering.
Because, no reason.
As a sister, of course.
That's what you meant!
Kotari.
What do you want?
I really like how those ribbons look on you.
Oh.
Well, thanks, big bro.
Hey, thanks for saving me.
If you and Yoshino hadn't come, I don't know what would have happened to Kotari.
Or origami, for that matter.
Hmm.
I just responded to your feelings.
I'm sure it was the same for Yoshino.
I hope you'll keep saving any other spirits that might appear.
Like you saved me.
And Yoshino.
And Kotari, too.
Sure.
I promise.
But, I wish you wouldn't kiss them.
I don't know why, but I don't like it when I see you kissing someone else.
What is that about?
It's such a weird feeling.
Well, let's see.
I don't know if I can explain it.
It's complicated.
I think you should just shut up and kiss me.
Oh, do you?
I do.
I really do.
Ooh, way to go, Yoshino.
Don't mind us.
Just keep on doing what you are about to do.
Why are you guys still watching me?
Ignore them.
I'm right here.
Kiss her!
To be continued.
Someday.
Kiss her!
Oh
能力で走り続けるよ
また会えますか 信じてくれますか
恋に似てひらるもので
成果は
世界が終わる前に生きる大きス
君が笑ってくれたら嬉しいのです